Now we have a Tessle spec. We'll use the
Tessle framework to generate our code
from and run the application.
I start by downloading my usage specs so
that my agent has the necessary context
to build. Next, I'll build my
application which will generate the code
for my application. During this process,
Claude identifies the specs in the
project and runs the build tool on
Tessle's MCP server for that spec.
Claude wants to run tests, but for now,
I'll test visually before creating my
robust test suite for this application.
Next, I want to create an entry point
for my application. For now, I'll have
Claude Code write some disposable code
to run this at a terminal. I'll finally
compile the generated TypeScript code,
and we're ready to test the app.
At a terminal, I can now test this
quickly to ensure the built application
is what I'm looking for. I'm not testing
for edge cases here. I'm just looking to
see that the core functionality is
correct. I play to see what happens when
I lose a game as well as win a game. And
I'll consider making some changes as
needed.
Now, I'll iteratively update my
application. In this case, using clawed
code to add and tune the functionality
and capabilities in my spec until I'm
satisfied with the application. I'm
requesting a styling change this time
around.
I can now test the application back in
the terminal. These rapid edit and test
cycles enable me to develop my
application while maintaining a specd-
driven development approach.
We now have a running application that
we have generated from a spec. The next
step is to create tests from my spec
requirements to make the application
robust.